Guide to the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection RG.11.4
New York University Archives
- Series XII: Building files: University Heights Center
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 13 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 20 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from John R. Ragazzini to Dr. J. M. Leise, 23 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from John M. O'Mara to Hamilton P. Smith, 24 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 25 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Tech. II Building Room Schedule, 27 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 31 May 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to John M. O'Mara, 2 June 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 2 June 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Robert C. Geldmacher, 13 June 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 24 June 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Kenneth B. Morris to Mr. Botho Schneider, 30 June 196 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 7 July 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 8 July 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 8 July 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dr. Joseph E. Schober, 16 June 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Robert C. Geldmacher to Hamilton Smith (Box 27)
    - Letter from Botho Schneider to NYU Plant & Properties, 18 November 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Donald W. Craig to Botho Schneider, 19 December 1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 17 January 1967 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Tech. II Building Project - Architects' Recommendations, 11 January 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Kenneth B. Morris to Hamilton P. Smith, 22 March 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Kenneth B. Morris, 31 March 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton P. Smith, 27 April 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 3 May 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 8 May 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Alexei Vergun to Martin L. Beck 1 June 1967 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 22 September 1967 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Series XIII: Building files: other university centers
  - Bennett Residence, Bronxville, N.Y., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Camp Sanita -- School of Education, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Dental Center, 1961-1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Dental Center, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Dental Center, 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Expansion Plans, 1962-1965 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Expansion Plans, 1966-1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Merrill Hall, 1967-1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Nichols Hall, 1956-1977 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- 68 Trinity Place, 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- 95 Trinity Place, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Fine Arts, 1962-1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Landscaping -- IFA, GBA, Dental Center, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Medical Center, 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center -- Professional Building (Kips Bay), 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Medical Center -- Brookdale Hall, Schwartz Lecture Hall, other [O], 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center -- NYU-Bellevue Slum Clearance, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Medical Center -- NYU-Bellevue Building Program Book, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - School of Education -- Hotel Beverly [50th St. & Lexington Ave.], undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Sterling Forest [University Valley] -- General Planning, 1961-1966 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Sterling Forest [UV] -- Inst. of Environmental/Industrial Medicine, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Sterling Forest [UV] -- Inst. of Environmental/Industrial Medicine, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Sterling Forest [University Valley] -- Housing, 1962-Apr 1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Sterling Forest [University Valley] -- Housing, 1963-May 1964 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Sterling Forest [UV] -- Admin. Bldg, Biology Labs, Geology Labs, 1962-1965 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Sterling Forest [UV]-- Timberhill: Moses Graduate Studies Center at Greenwood Lake, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - White Plains Center -- Division of General Education, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Series XIV: Building files: Washington Square neighborhood and non-NYU properties
  - 692 Broadway, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University -- Planning Report, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Square, 1966-1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Grace Church School, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 10 Gracie Square South -- Penthouse -- Albert Gordon, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 262 Greene Street, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Greenwich Village Housing Development, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Greenwich Village Buildings -- Drawings by Roberto [O], undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Greenwich Village Buildings -- Greeting Card Depictions, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Greenwich Village Maps, 1944-1960s (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Kips Bay I [136 E. 16th St.] -- Doctors= Offices -- Dr. Horowitz, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Kips Bay II [333 E. 30th St.] -- Doctors= Offices -- Dr. Meltzer, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Kips Bay II [333 E. 30th St.] -- Doctors= Offices -- Dr. Meltzer, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lockwood-Matthews Mansion, Norwalk CT, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Manhattan Buildings -- Roberto Services Invoices, 1983-1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Manhattan, Lower -- Drawings by Roberto, Maps, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mead Hall, Drew University, NJ -- Restoration, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Mead Hall, Drew University, NJ -- Restoration, 1981-1984 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - New York City Public Housing, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - New York City Urban Renewal -- Brochures, 1954-1959 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - New York City Zoning, 1959-1974 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Old Merchant's House -- Restoration, 1974-1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Corlear's Hook -- Slum Clearance, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Seward Park -- Slum Clearance, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Town Hall -- Plaques, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Union Square Subway Station [O], 1975-1982 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Washington Square Church -- Restoration, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Washington Square -- Drawings by Roberto, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation -- Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation -- Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation -- Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation, 1960-1963 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Washington Square Park -- Renovation, 1965-1970 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Washington Square Neighborhood Street Lighting, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Washington Square Neighborhood Street Lighting, Jan 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Washington Square Neighborhood Street Lighting, Sep 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Washington Square Neighborhood Street Lighting, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Washington Square Neighborhood Street Lighting, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Washington Square Southeast Urban Renewal Project, 1962-1967 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Waterside Housing Development -- Brochure, ca.1970 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - World Trade Center -- Brochures, Articles [O], 1960-1967 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Series XV: Architect, engineer, and builder promotional materials
  - Sol Cornberg Associates, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Eggers & Higgins, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Fellheimer & Wagner, 1962-1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Fletcher-Thompson, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Fordyce & Hamby, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Frederick G. Frost & Associates, 1962-1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Francis X. Gina Associates, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Frank Grad & Sons, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - William A. Hall, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Howell, Lewis, Shay & Associates, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Jones & Mogensen, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Seymour R. Joseph, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Kahn & Jacobs, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Walter Kidde Construction, Inc., 1962 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - James King & Sons, 1959-1964 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Kruse, Flaherty & Associates, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Kump Associates, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - LaPierre, Litchfield & Partners, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - William Lescaze, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Levy & O=Keefe, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Joseph R. Loring & Associates, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Bernard A. Marson, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Moore & Hutchins, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Guy B. Panero, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Paul & Jarmul, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Perkins & Will, 1961-1965 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Phillips Associates, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Raymond & Rado, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Rockrise & Watson, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Rogers & Butler, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - H. Sand & Co., 1961 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Sasaki, Walker & Associates, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Seelye, Stevenson, Value & Knecht, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Sharp & Handren/Ketchen & Sharp, 1958-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Sherwood, Mills & Smith, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Shreve, Lamb & Harmon, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Slingerland & Booss, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Slocum & Fuller, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Stelling, Lord-Wood & VanSuetendael, 1958-1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Richard Wilson Snibbe, 1962-1966 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Paolo E. Squassi, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Lieberfeld & Heldman, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Tippetts, Abbett, McCarthy, Stratton -- Charles B. Ferris Assocs., undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Tizian Associates, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Emanuel N. Turano, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Turner Construction Company, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Max O. Urbahn, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Victor M. Villemain, 1962-1964 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Vogel & Strunk, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Wank Adams Slavin & Associates, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - John Carl Warnecke & Associates, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Warner Burns Toan Lunde, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Warner Burns Toan Lunde, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Wechsler & Schimenti, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Frederic P. Wiedersum Associates, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Yamasaki & Associates, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Zion & Breen, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Series XVI: Oversize
  - Washington Square South -- Drawing by Roberto, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Building Material, Structural Requirement Charts, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center -- Cooperative-Ambulatory Care Pavilion Schematic Drawings Book, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - World Trade Center -- Proposal Books, 1960-1967 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Zoning Resolution of the City of New York, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Design Book, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Property Map, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - University Heights Master Plan, Harlem River Development Drawings, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Arch -- Drawings by Roberto, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 53 Washington Square South -- John Sloan Studio -- Drawings by Roberto, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 4, Box Shared University Archives 091)
  - Washington Square North -- Drawings by Roberto, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Bobst/ Washington Square Library -- Site Zoning Schematic Drawing, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Building Drawing, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Broadway-Waverly Place-Washington Place-Mercer Street Block -- Copies of Building Forms, 1890-1894 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Union Square Subway Station -- Floor Plans, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Worcester CBD Project, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Design Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Deutches Haus -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 42 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Deutches Haus -- Plans, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Deutches Haus -- Plans, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Hall of Fame Memorial Court -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - School of Education, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Hall of Fame Pavilion -- Images, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - University Heights -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 1, Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Plans, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lettering, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - University Heights Maps, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Unidentifed Building Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square Campus Map, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Business School Drawing, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Havemeyer Hall -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - University Heights -- Site Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Classroom Building, WSC -- Plams, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Engineering Center, University Heights -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - The Student Dormitory, University Heights -- Plans, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Gould Student Center -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Henry Ford Engineering Center, undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Gould Student Center, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Images of Washington Square Campus and University Heights, undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Bobst Library -- Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 24, Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 7)
  - Office Building -- Floor Plans, undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - NYU Law Center -- Plans, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Kevorkian Center -- Plans, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - NYU Residence Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Buildings -- Plans, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - University Heights Maps, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics and Aerospace, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Letter from President, Secretary, Treasurer, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Plans, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - University Heights Maps, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawings, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Schematic Design for Proposed Jewish Center, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Plans, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - NYU Buildings Drawings, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Architecture Articles from NYU Publications, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - University Christian Foundation -- Plans, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - 23-29 Washington Place -- Chemistry Labs -- Plans, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Club, University Heights -- Plans, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - 3 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Sedgwick Ave Residence -- Plans, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Lettering, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - The Westsider, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Planning Recommendations for Washington Square Area, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Building Program--Bellevue Medical Center, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - University Heights Buildings -- Drawings, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Judson Block -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Pavillion infront of Warren Weaver Hall -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Addition to Kimmell Center -- Drawing/Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Center, 2nd Floor -- Plans, 1970 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Center, 1st Floor -- Plans, 1970 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bernstein Hall, Rm 265 -- Plans, 1969 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bernstein Hall, Rm 265 -- Plans, 1969 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Model of University Heights -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology I (proposed), University Heights -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology II (proposed), University Heights -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Classroom with projector -- Sketch, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - New York City looking NW over Washington Square Park -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Model of School of Education (proposed) -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building, Clerestory Floor Plan, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building, 4th & 5th Floor Plan, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Interior of La Maison Francaise -- Sketch, 1978 (Folder 5)
  - Group Living Plan II, Exterior -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Final Program Development, University Heights -- Map, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Sports Center (proposed), Washington Square Campus -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Sports Center (proposed), Washington Square Campus -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Brookdale Hall -- Drawing, 1973 (Drawer RA 5)
  - 13-19 University Place Offices -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kimball Hall, Main Entrance -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kimball Hall, Main Entrance -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kimball Hall, Main Entrance -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bobst Exterior looking SE -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bobst Exterior looking straight on -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bobst Exterior looking straight on -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bobst Exterior looking SE (close up) -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kimball Hall Exterior with New Entrance -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Medical Center -- Map, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Fraternity House, Exterior, University Heights -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Model of Washington Square Campus -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawing of a House by J. Roberto, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Center, Conference Room -- Plans, 1970 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Entrance Institute of Accounting Research -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Institute of Accounting Research, Conference Room-- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Institute of Accounting Research, Research Assitant Office -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Institute of Accounting Research, Professor's Office -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Institute of Accounting Research, Library -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Institute of Accounting Research, Library -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tisch Hall, Meyer Hall of Physics, Sign Location -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Graduate School Apartment, Suggested Room Layouts and Furniture -- Images, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Unidentified Building -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Elevation, South Wall, Fountain Room -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
    Separated Materials
    Moved to flat file cases. See Guide to Oversized Materials for location.
  - Kevorkian Center, South Wall Library -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, South Wall Library -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Ceiling, Foyer -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Ceiling, Foyer -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Entrance, Foyer -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Entrance, Foyer -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center, Entrance, Foyer -- Drawing, 1976 (Drawer RA 5)
    Moved to flat file cases. See Guide to Oversized Materials for location.Moved to flat file cases. See Guide to Oversized Materials for location.
  - Linguistics Quarter, 10 Washington Pl -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Drawings of Lounge Furniture for lounges and study, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Vanderbilt Hall, Ornamental Staircase -- Drawing, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Bernstein Hall -- Study Sketch, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Student Residence Hall Conversion, Washington Square Campus -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Student Residence Hall Conversion, Washington Square Campus -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Student Residence Hall Conversion, Washington Square Campus -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Student Residence Hall Conversion, Washington Square Campus -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Longterm Development Plan -- Map, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Merril Hall (proposed) -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Washington Square Campus -- Map (negative), undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Student Residence Hall (proposed), University Heights -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Memorial Gateway -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, partial close-up of front -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, partial close-up of front -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, partial close-up of front -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - South Building and 80 Washington Square East -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - South Building and 80 Washington Square East -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - South Building and 80 Washington Square East -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Fillmore, East -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Washington Square Park looking East -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Right Corner of Main Building, Washington Square College -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Hall of Philosophy facade -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Location for New Signs on campus -- Image, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Campus -- Aerial Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Campus -- Aerial Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Campus -- Aerial Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)